Guide to the Theta Delta Chi records, 1872-2014.
Theta Delta Chi records, 1872-2014.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Theta Delta Chi records, 1872-2014.
37-4-1602
Theta Delta Chi. Beta Charge (Cornell University)
5.9 cubic ft.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes photographs, mostly of fraternity members; pamphlets about the fraternity; records of the fraternity's Building Fund Campaign; and other correspondence and miscellaneous records of Theta Delta Chi at Cornell University. Also includes scrapbooks kept by Luzerne Coville (Class of 1886) and Charles Rodman Stull (Class of 1907); and copies of the chapter newsletter, The Beta Bulletin, 1981-2015.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes photographs, mostly of fraternity members; pamphlets about the fraternity; records of the fraternity's Building Fund Campaign; and other correspondence and miscellaneous records of Theta Delta Chi at Cornell University. Also includes scrapbooks kept by Luzerne Coville (Class of 1886) and Charles Rodman Stull (Class of 1907); and copies of the chapter newsletter, The Beta Bulletin, 1981-2015.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Theta Delta Chi.; Coville, Luzerne.; Stull, Charles Rodman.; Cornell University -- Societies, etc.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.; Greek letter societies; Societies
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access restricted to the president, secretary and librarian of Theta Delta Chi.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Series 1: Financial Correspondence
Series II. Series II: General Documents and Correspondence
Series III. Series 3: Photos
CONTAINER LIST
- Series 1: Financial Correspondence (Box Box, Folder Folder)
  - Financial Correspondence, Expression (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 4-12)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1923-1931 (Box 1, Folder 13-21)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1923-1931 (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
- Series II: General Documents and Correspondence
  - Correspondence Between Chapters, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Between Chapters, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Between Chapters, 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Banquet Programs, 1883-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Reports- Beta Charge of Delta Chi, 1920-1930 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- Office of the President, 1900-1902 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1900-1902 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Information, 1895-1923 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Metal Finial with Horse Head, Undated (Box 2)
  - Beta Charge of Theta Delta Chi- Minutes, 1895-1906 (Box 2)
  - History and Biographical Catalogue of the Beta Charge of Theta Delta Chi, 1900 (Box 2)
  - Blueprints and Correspondence, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Programs and Letters, 1883-1901 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlets and Loose Pages, 1882-1891 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence on Theta Delta Chi Letterhead, 1922-1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Forms for Membership Catalogue, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Forms for Membership Catalogue, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to E.W. Huffcut, 1900-1907 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1872-1932 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1879-1900 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1887-1895 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1890-1897 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1878-1906 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Papers for Theta Delta Chi Article, 1879-1900 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - G.L. Newsletters, 1896-11-1898-07 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer Reports and Invoices, 1890-1922 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer Reports and Invoices, 1890-1922 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - G.L. Newsletters, 1898-02-1900-02 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1897-1899 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Archives, 1897-1902 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence in Envelopes, 1900-1907 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets and Newsletters, 1870-1932 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1884-1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1895-1946 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees of Beta Charge of Theta Delta Chi Minutes, 1895-1901 (Box 3)
  - Theta Delta Chi Treasurer's Book, 1887 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to Corbin, 1872-1873 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dickenson Letters, 1870's, 1873-1875 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Corbin Letters, 1872-1875 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Letters Relating to the Founding of Beta Chapter, 1895-1900 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1870-1891 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dickinson Letters, 1868-1869 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Wadhams Letters, 1870-1871 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Huffcut to Stone, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fitch Letters, 1870-1873 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Restoration Report for Theta Delta Chi House, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Beta Bulletin, 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Beta Bulletin, 1988-1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Beta Bulletin, 1997-2005 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Beta Bulletin, 2006-2015 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1885-1895 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Half of photo from 1895
  - Scrapbook, 1885-1886 (Box 6)
  - Scrapbook kept by an unidentified member of Theta Delta Chi, 1882-1889 (Box 6)
    Fragile, tied with ribbon
  - Scrapbook kept by Charles Rodman Stull, a member of Theta Delta Chi, 1907 (Box 6)
- Series 3: Photos
  - Wallet Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1873-1880 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Found in original envelopes, only one original kept because of written information on envelope
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1890-1897 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1885-1898 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1887-1905 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1884-1904 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1881-1898 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1878-1900 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1891-1902 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1887-1906 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1890-1898 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photos of Fraternity Brothers, 1888-1902 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photos of Buildings and Classrooms with Students, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photos of Buildings and Classrooms, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photos of Women and Men in Drag, 1888-1899 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photos of Fraternity Objects, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Portraits, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photos of Buildings and Classrooms with Students, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photo of Crew Teams, 1888-1889 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photos of Albert W. Smith, 1874-1877 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photo of Murray Norcross Shelton, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 1)